Guide to the William R. and Louise Fielder Sheet Music Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 24. Military, 19th Century
  - Subseries b. General
    - The two pickets Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1863.Cincinnati: John Church, Jr. ,1863 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Engraver H. F. Greene, Engr.
      Performed by Ossian E. Dodge and William Hayward
      Also published by Firth, Pond & Co., New York; J. C. Haynes & Co., Boston; and J. E. Gould, Philadelphia.
    - We're tending to the old camp ground: song and chorus Boston: Henry Tolman & Co.,1864 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Words and Music by J. W. Turner
    - Victory at last!, as sung at the raising of the old Flag, on Fort Sumter, April 14th, 1865 New York: William A. Pond & Co.,1865 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Music by William B. Bradbury
      Words by Mrs. M. A. Kidder
    - Lord Nelson's hornpipe, composed and arranged for the piano forte Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,n.d. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - La Marseillaise s.l.: s.d.,n.d. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Jullien's American quadrille 'Our flag is there' New York: S. C. Jollie,1853.London: Jullien & Co. ,1853 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Lithographer: George E. Leefe, New York
      Also published by William Hall & Son, New York
    - The banner's unfurled Baltimore: John Cole,n.d. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Composed by Arthur F. Keene
      Written by Doctor Arnold of Port Antinio Isle of Jamaica
    - Capt. Andrews' quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1843 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Composed and Arranged by C. L. Holbrook
    - Bigelow's quick step, dedicated to Capt. George Tyler Bigelow, the officers & members of the New England guards Boston: Henry Prentiss,1839 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Arranged by John Holloway
      Lithographer: Thomas Moore's Lithog., Boston
    - Grafted into the army Chicago: Root & Cady,1862 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Lithographer: Chas. Shober, Chicago
    - Dixie's nurse: song Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,1865 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Composed by M. E.
      Words by Eastburn
    - The retreat quick step, in imitation of drums, fifes, and bugles Philadelphia: A. Fiot,1840 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Composed by Loisa Puget
    - Congress grand march New York: E. Riley,n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Composed and Arranged by J. Z. Hesser
    - The soldier's grave, monody on the death of Sir John Moore New York: Firth Pond & Co.,[1848 -1855] (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Music by Thomas Williams
      Poetry by Rev. Charles Wolfe
    - Battle of Waterloo, composed and dedicated to the Duke of Wellington Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,[1858 -1876] (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Arranged by G. Anderson
    - The John Brown song, or, Glory hallelujah, with nw and revised words Chicago: Root & Cady,1861.New York: William Hall & Son ,1861 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Also published by Firth, Pond & Co., New York; Russell & Tolman, Boston; S. Brainard & Co., Cleveland; H. N. Hempsted, Milwaukee.
    - Soldier's tear New York: Firth & Hall,1832 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Music by Alexander Lee
      Words by Thomas H. Bayley
    - Maryland, my Maryland Philadelphia: Sep. Winner,1862 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Adapted and arranged by Sep. Winner
    - Is that mother bending o'er me: song and chorus St. Louis: W. M. Harlow,1863 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Music by Charles H. Greene
    - Music of the union, a medley on American national airs Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1861.Boston: C. C. Clapp & Co. ,1861 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Arranged by Charles Grobe
      Also published by Beck & Lawton, Philadelphia; Firth Pond, & Co., New York; and John Church, Jr., Cincinnati.
    - Avezzana's quick step New York: Millet's Music Saloon,1845 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Composed by C. Chianei
      Lithographer: Louis L. Bishop, daguerrotype; Lith. of Michelin, New York
      Performed by American Brass Band
    - God save America: a grand national ode in honor of the glorious anniversary of American independence New York: G. Endicott,1835 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Ardapted and arranged by J. Watson
      Performed by Mr & Miss Watson, Signor Ravaglia and Mrs. Archer at Niblos Garden
    - General McClellan's grand march Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,1861 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Company 6 quick step New York: William Horn & Company,1841 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Composed by C. S. Graffula
      Lithographer: Lieut. Cozzens, del.; G. W. Lewis Lith., New York
    - Battle of Port Royal, or, the Bonbardment of Forts Walker & Beauregard Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1861 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Gov. Wright's grand match Boston: Willaim H. Oakes,1844.Boston: E. H. Wade ,1844 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Composed by Oliver J. Shaw
      Lithographer: E. Lintzenich, del.; Thayer & Co.'s Lithog., Boston
    - Worcester guards quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1840 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Composed by Samuel R. Leland
      Lithographer: Thayer & Co.'s Lithog., Boston
    - The prize banner quick step Boston: Prentiss,1847 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Lithographer: Thayer's Lith., Boston
      Prentiss collection of Marches and Quick steps
    - Zampa quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1840 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Military movements
    - Manhattan Beach march Cincinnati, New York, Chicago: John Church Company,1893 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Composed by John Philip Sousa
    - General Boulanger's march New York: Spear & Denhoff,1887 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Music by C. L. Desormes
      Arranged by Vrai Gautier
      Lithographer: Cosack & Co., Buffalo, NY
    - Grand centennial march Boston: C. Bradlee,1830 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Lithographer: M. E. D. Brown, del.; Pendleton's Lith.
      Performed by Boston Bands
    - The tri-colored quadrilles New York: J. L. Hewitt,1830 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - The veterans New York: Hitchcock and McCargo Publishing Comany, Limited,1890 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Composed by William W. Badger
      Lithographer: George H. Walker & Co., Lith., Boston
    - Capt. Pray's quick step, arranged for and dedicated to the Hancock Light Infantry Boston: H. Prentiss,1844 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Arranged by William C. Glynn
      Lithographer: Thayer & Co.'s Lithography
    - The Blue's quick step [2 copies] Boston: John Ashton & Co.,1836 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Composed by John Holloway
      Lithographer: G. L. Brown, invt.; Moore's Lithography, Boston
    - Roxbury horse guard's quick step Boston: Henry Tolman,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Composed by Theo. Weber
      Lithographer: L. Prang & Co., Lith., Boston
    - Sever's quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1846 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Composed by J. H. Seipp
      Lithographer: W. Sharp & Co.
    - General Townsend's grand calvalry march Boston: George P. Reed,1846.Albany: F. J. Ilsley & Co. ,1846 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Composed and Arranged by C. L. Underner
      Lithographer: Bufford's & Co., Lith., Boston
    - Rough & Ready: a patriotic song, dedicated to General Zachary Taylor Boston: W. H. Oakes & E. H. Wade,1847 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Words by Major Norton
    - The song of the drum, from 'Il figlia del reggimento' New York: William Hall & Son,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Words by C. Jefferys
      From :La fille du regiment
    - The bride-elect march Cincinnati, New York, Chicago, Leipsig: John Church Company,1897 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Music by John Philip Sousa
    - Warren phalanx quick step Boston: H. Prentiss,1838 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Composed by S. Knaebel
      Lithographer: R. Cooke, del.; Moore's Lith., Boston
      Performed by Boston Brass Band
    - Hall's quick step Boston: Oakes & Swan,1840 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Composed and Arranged by T. Bricher
      Lithographer: R. Cooke, del.; Thayer's Lithography, Boston
    - The citizen's quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1838 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Composed by J. Holloway
      Lithographer: R. Cooke, del.; T. Moore's Lith., Boston
    - Shamut quick step Boston: George P. Reed,[1840] (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Composed by T. Bricher
    - Andrew's quick step Boston: George P. Reed,1840 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Camp-Sargent quick step Boston: George P. Reed,1840 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Arranged by A. F. Knight
      Performed by Boston Light Infantry
    - March of the First volunteer regiment of Alabama Boston: C. Bradlee,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Lithographer: R. Cooke, del.; T. Moore's Lithography, Boston
    - The flag with thirty four stars, or, Hurrah! for the dear old flag with every stripe and star: a patriotic song with chorus ad-lib Cincinnati: A. C. Peters & Bro.,1862.St. Louis: J. L. Peters & Bro. ,1862 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Composed and Arranged by Prof. C. S. Root
      Written by Gen. G. Horner, Esq.
    - Seminary quick step Boston: Keith's Music Publishing House,1844 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Composed and Arranged by Charles E. Bennett
    - Le carneval de New York: variations burlesques sur le thème favorit du H. Vieuxtemps 'Yankee Doodle' Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,n.d.New York: J. E. Gould & Co. ,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Composed by D. Krug
    - The battle-cry of freedom Chicago: Root & Cady,1862 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Also published by S. Brainard, Cleveland; H. Tolman & Co., Boston; and H. N. Hempsted, Milwaukee.
    - Sans souci: galop di bravura Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1871.Chicago: Lyon & Healy ,1871 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Music by J. M. Wehli
      Also published by J. Church & Co., Cincinnati; J. C. Haynes & Co., Boston; and Lee & Walker, Philadelphia.
    - Pulawski march for the piano forte New York: Antonio C. Martinz,1839 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Composed by Antonio C. Martinz
    - The Washington Light Infantry quick step Boston: John Ashton & co.,1836 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Ocean wave quick step New York: Firth, Hall, & Pond ,1843.New York: Firth & Hall ,1843 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Lithographer: G. & W. Endicott
      Performed by Dodworths National Brass Band
    - Ocean wave quick step New York: James L. Hewitt & Co.,1843.New York: Firth & Hall ,1843 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - The American boy: a new patriotic song from the American sentinel Philadelphia: Osbourn's Music Saloon,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Composed by Francis Johnson
      Lithographer: Lehman & Duval, Lith., Philadelphia
    - Old Ironsides: a glee composed on the ocaion of the rebuilding and filling out anew of the United States Frigate Constitution, respectfully dedicated to the Officers of the American Navy New York: Firth & Hall,1834 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Music by E. Ives, Jr.
      Poetry by Miss S. W. Perry
    - Oliver's quick step Boston: H. Prentiss,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Music by Nichols
      Arranged by B. A. Burditt
    - New England guards quick step, dedicated to Capt. Thomas Dwight, the officers and members of the corps Boston: John Ashton & Co.,1835 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Music by Charles Zeuner
    - Mechanic Phalanx quick step, performed with great success on their anniversary, July 4th, 1841 Lowell: J. N. Metcalf,1841.Boston: William H. Oakes ,1841 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Composed by Benjamin F. Baker
      Lithographer: Thayer & Co. Lithography, Boston
      Performed by Methuen Brass Band
    - Crafted into the army Chicago: Root & Cady,1862 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - The stars and stripes forever! march Cincinnati, New York, Chicago, Leipsic: John Church Company,1897 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Song of the death of Col. Ellsworth: the gallant zouave Philadelphia: J. Magee,1861 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Marche des zouaves composée pour le piano à deux mains Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Composed by Charles John
    - United States zouave cadets quick step Chicago: Root & Cady,1860.Boston: Russell & Tolman ,1860 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Music by A. J. Vaas
      Lithographer: Ed. Mendel, Lith., Chicago
      Also published by William Hall & Son, New York; W. G. Peters & Son, Cincinnati; D. P. Faulds & Co., Louisville; and H. N. Hempsted, Milwaukee.
    - Col. Ellsworth funeral march Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,1861 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Thirteenth Minnesota Infantry march s.l.: s.d.,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Music by Antonio G. Escamilla
      Lithographer: Lit. de Chofrey Co.
    - Columbia, the gem of the ocean Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,[1861].Philadelphia: G. Willig ,1843 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Arranged by T. A. Becket, Esq.
    - Buena Vista triumphal march, on a theme from the opera of the Jewess composed for the piano forte and respectfully dedicated to Major General Taylor Cincinnati: Schatzman & Brulon,1847 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Composed by Carl Fritz
    - Dixie for the union New York: Firth, Pond & Co.,1861 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Melody by Dan D. Emmett
      Words by Francis J. Crosby
    - Marching through Georgia: song and chorus Chicago: Root & Cady,1865 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Sabre and spurs: march of the American Cavalry Cleveland: Sam Fox Publishing Co.,1918.London: Bosworth & Co. ,1918 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - National guard's banner song Boston: Geo. Willig, Jr.,1843 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Adapted by H. Dielman
      Written by W. H. Carpenter
      Lithographer: A. C. Smith; E. Weber & Co.
    - To the west: national song arranged as a solo and quartette Philadelphia: Winner & Shuster,1854 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Composed by H. R.
      Written by C. M.
      Engraver R. M. Gaw, Eng.
      Performed by Charles Swain, Esq.
    - Herculean quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Whipple's quick step Boston: Keith's Music Publishing House,1845 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Composed by Charles F. Heuberer
    - Lorena Chicago: H. M. Higgins,1862 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Music by J. P. Webster
      Poetry by Rev. H. D. L. Webster
      Lithographer: Charles Shober, Lith., Chicago
    - Corporal schnapps: song and chorus Cleveland: S. Brainard's Sons,1864 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Written and composed by Henry C. Work
    - The bugle quick-step s.l.: s.d.,n.d. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - The minute gun at sea: a favorite duett New York: Firth, Pond & Co.,[1854] (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Composed by M. P. King
    - Gordon's quick step Boston: Charles H. Keith,1842 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Composed by Zetzsche
      Arranged by S. Knaebel
      Lithographer: Thayer & Co.
    - Sans souci: galop de bravoure Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Lithographer: T. Sinclair's Lith.
    - General Persifor F. Smith's march Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1848 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Music by T. J. Martin
    - The battle of Resaca de la Palma Baltimore: George Willig, Jr.,1848 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Music by John Schell
      Lithographer: E. Weber & Co., Baltimore
    - Tramp! Tramp! Tramp! (the prisoner's hope) Chicago: Root & Cady,1864 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Lithographer: Copcutt & Williams
    - La Marseillaise Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,1859 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Arranged by Ferd. Beyer
      From :American National Airs
    - The Washington Post march Philadelphia: Harry Coleman,1889 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Hail Columbia: brilliant transcription for the piano Philadelphia: G. Andre & Co.,[1858 -1875] (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Composed by Charles Voss
    - How are you, conscript? Boston: Henry Tolman & Co.,1868.Chicago: Root & Cady ,1868 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Words and Music by Frank Wilder
      Also published by W. F. Sherwin, Albany; and W. Hall & Son, New York.
    - We never can forget it, or, the memories of Andersonville prison pens New York: W. Jennings Demorest,1865.Chicago: Root & Cady ,1865 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Also published by Lee & Walker, Philadelphia; O. Ditson & Co., Boston; W. Hall & Son, New York; S. T. Gordon, New York; Wm. A. Pond & Co., New York; Horace Waters, New York; and Firth Son & Co.,Ê New York.
    - General McClellans farewell to the army of the Potomac Philadelphia: Lee & Walker,1863 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Music by H. Coyle
      Words by E. W. H.
    - Under the daisies: ballad New York: S. T. Gordon & Son,1865 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Words by Hattie Tyng Griswold
    - The vacant chair Chicago: Root & Cady,1862 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Lithographer: Corputt & Williams
    - Major General McClellan's grand march Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1861 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - La fille du régiment: fantasie brillante pour piano Offenbach: Chez Jean Andre;,n.d.Lourdes: Ewer & Co. ,n.d. (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Also published by Brandus & Co., Paris; G. A. Augener & Co. and Ricordi, Milan; and G. Andre; & Co., Philadelphia.
    - Qui vive: grand galop de concert Philadelphia: F. A. North & Co.,1869.Washington: W. G. Metzerott & Co. ,1869 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Composed by W. Ganz
      Arranged by T. a'Becket
      Lithographer: F. Perring
      Also published by R. S. Poppen, St. Louis.
    - United States Marine march New York: Oliver Ditson & Co.,[1844 -1857] (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Composed by A lady of Charleston
    - Rosecrans' victory march Cincinnati: John Church, Jr.,1863 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Music by Charles R. Crosby
    - The stars and stripes forever: brilliant variations of the Star Spangled Banner [3 copies] Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1854.New York: C. H. Ditson & Co. ,1854 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Printer Warren, Music Stereotyper, New York
      Also published by John Church, Jr., Cincinnati; J. E. Gould, Philadelphia; and J. C. Haynes & Co., Boston.
    - The Star Spangled Banner, for four voices or chorus New York: William Hall & Son,[1859 -1870] (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Lithographer: Pearson & Melville, New York
      National Songs arranged for four voices or chorus, for the use of Musical Societies
    - Yankee Doodle, with concert variations New York: William Hall & Son,1852 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Music by Maurice Strakosch
    - The striped pig New York: Hewitt & Jaques,[1834] (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Performed by Mr. Wills at the Tremont Theatre, Boston
    - Tyler's quick step Worcester: Leland & Putnam,1842 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Composed by David Perry
      Arranged by S[amuel] R. Leland
      Lithographer: B. W. Thayer & Co.'s Lith., Boston
    - Newton's quick step Boston: Keith's Music Publishing House,1844 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Composed and Arranged by Samuel R. Leland
      Performed by Worcester Brass Band
    - General Bertrand's quick step New York: Firth & Hall,1843.New York: James L. Hewitt & Co. ,1843 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Composed by Robert McKinstry, Jr.
      Arranged by George F. Bristow
    - The liberty bell march Cincinnati: John Church Company,1893 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Naval reserve (la reserva naval) march s.l.: Joseph Sancho,1893.San Francisco: Broder & Schlam, Music Publishers ,1893 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Composed by Joseph Sancho
    - Get out of the wilderness and dixie's land: two popular airs Cincinnati: John Church, Jr.,1890.Philadelphia: Lee & Walker ,1890 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Arranged by Paul Jones
      Performed by Captain A. Menter and his American Cornet Band
      Also published by Oliver Ditson & Co., Boston and Firth, Pond & Co., New York.
    - La Marseillaise, with brilliant variations Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1856.Cincinnati: John Church, Jr. ,1856 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Weeping, sad and lonely, or, when this cruel war is over: song and chorus Brooklyn: Sawyer & Thomson,1863.Philadelphia: Lee & Walker ,1863 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Composed and Arranged by Henry Tucker
      Words by Charles Carroll Sawyer
      Performed by Wood's Minstrels, New York
      Alsopublished by Hall & Son, New York; S. T. Gordon, New York; Wm. A. Pond, New York; and Oliver Ditson, Boston.
    - The stars and stripes forever! march Cincinnati, New York, Chicago, Leipsic: John Church Company,1897 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Non piu andrai: air militaire du Mariage de Figaro de Mozart (the celebrated military air of Mozart) New York: Dubois & Stodart,[1828 -1834] (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Arranged by H. Lemoine
    - The conscript's departure 'Jeannette & Jeannot' New York: William Hall & Son,[1848 -1851].Boston: George P. Reed & Co. ,[1839 -1852] (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Also published by Lee & Walker, Philadelphia.
    - General Sigel's grand march Cleveland and Chicago: S. Brainard's Sons,1862 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Lithographer: Johns & Co., Lith., Cleveland
      Popular Marches, Battle Pieces Etc. for Piano or Organ
    - The conscript's departure: 'Jeannette & Jeannot' quadrilles, new and complete edition New York: Firth, Pond & Co.,[1840 -1855].St. Louis: Balmer & Weber ,n.d. (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Also published by W. T. Mayo, New Orleans.
    - The star spangled banner: song and chorus with an additional verse (5th) Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1861.Boston: C. C. Clapp & Co. ,1861 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Additional verse by Dr. O. W. Holmes
      Lithographer: Bufford's Lith.
      National Music
      Also published by Beck & Lawton, Philadelphia; Firth Pond & Co., New York; and John Church, Jr., Cincinnati.
    - Viva l'America, home of the free New York: William A. Pond & Co.,1889 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Music by Harrison Millard
      The Union Forever
    - The Boyleston quadrilles Boston: T. Comer,1836 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Arranged by T. Comer
      La Somnambula, Maid of Judah and the Tiger quick step
      L'Amina: from La Somnambula --Ivanhoe: from Maid of Judah --La Matilde / composed by T. Comer --Elvino --La Finale / composed by T. Comer
    - Rangers encampment quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1839 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Lithographer: Frederick Charlton; T. Moore's Lithog., Boston
      Performed by The Brass Band at the Encampment at Nashua, August 1, 1839
    - The Norfolk guards quick step Boston: William H. Oakes,1840 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Composed by George O. Farmer
      Lithographer: Sharp & Michelin
      Performed by The Boston Brigade Band
    - Sigourney's quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,[1837] (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Composed and Arranged by S. Knaebel
      Lithographer: C. Hubbard, del.; T. Moore's Lithography, Boston
    - Howard's quick step Boston: Stephen W. Marsh,1848 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Lithographer: J. H. Bufford's Lith.; daguerrotype by Chase
    - Sutton's quick step Boston: Parker & Ditson,1837 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Lithographer: Jenkins & Colbun's Lith.
    - Cadwalader's quick step Philadelphia: G. F. Hupfeld & Son,1840 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Composed by G. F. Hupfeld
      Lithographer: Wagner & McGuigan, Philadelphia
    - General McClennan's grand march Cincinnati: A. C. Peters & Bro.,1864.St. Louis: J. L. Peters & Bro. ,1864 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Composed by Donizetti
      Arranged by F. Muller
      Lithographer: Eaton & Weber
    - Bartlett's quick step Boston: C. H. Keith,1842 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Composed by Dr. John C. Bartlett of Chelmsford
    - Wood up quick step Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,n.d. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Composed and Arranged by John Holloway
    - The celebrated love not quick step Boston: Keith's Music Publishing House,1845 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Arranged by J. H. Seipp
    - Young buglers galop: four hands Dayton: J. Fischer & Bro.,1872.Milwaukee: Eugene Kuchele ,1872 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Composed by Karl Merz
      Lithographer: Dawley, New York
      Also published by Benham Bros., Indianapolis; C. J. Whitney & Co., Detroit; and A. J. Mitchell, Grand Rapids.
    - The battle march of Delhi: descriptive of the triumphant entry into Delhi London: Edwin Ashdown (Limited),n.d. (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Arranged by John Pridham
    - Glory, glory hallelujah: the popular refrain Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1861.New York: Firth, Pond & Co. ,1861 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Performed by Federal Volunteers
      Also published by J. Church, Jr., Cincinnati; J. C. Haynes & Co., Boston; J. E. Gould, Philadelphia; and C. C. Clapp & Co., Boston.
    - Prize banner quick step Boston: Henry Prentiss,1841 (Box 35, Folder 3)